linkne.ws 2012-11-09

# Privacy Policy - Solutions for Hair Loss | Hair Loss Solutions

* * *

* * *

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, solutionsforhairloss.org collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. solutionsforhairloss.org’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how solutionsforhairloss.org’s visitors use its website. From time to time, solutionsforhairloss.org may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

solutionsforhairloss.org also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blog.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to solutionsforhairloss.org’s websites choose to interact with solutionsforhairloss.org in ways that require solutionsforhairloss.org to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that solutionsforhairloss.org gathers depends on the nature of the interaction.  In each case, solutionsforhairloss.org collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with solutionsforhairloss.org.  solutionsforhairloss.org does not disclose personally-identifying information.  And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

solutionsforhairloss.org may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites.  However, solutionsforhairloss.org does not disclose personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. solutionsforhairloss.org uses cookies to help solutionsforhairloss.org identify and track visitors, their usage of solutionsforhairloss.org website, and their website access preferences. solutionsforhairloss.org visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using solutionsforhairloss.org’s website, with the drawback that certain features of solutionsforhairloss.org’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by solutionsforhairloss.org and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Thanks to [Automattic](http://automattic.com/) for Sample Privacy Policy
